Know they're all morons, right?
All they know maybe it's just a delete the strings
Yeah, I think the funny thing was it wasn't the guy was it wasn't the caller the person that came on
It wasn't the caller they came it was Denise news. There's like these news D
Hey flirty when I come on panel, you know, I want you to spend yourself
Why did you let it to say something? I know I know it was because it was all these saying it
So when I kicked him out of the studio, it was still all these saying it because that has had the banner up
It was like kind of a coordinated kind of thing
So I didn't try to I cut it off, but it was still all these saying it. That's why I
See nemesis
I thought I'd never listen well, what do you mean? I never I mean it's like I did I put up the banner and it was Aldi
It was Aldi, so you're saying I shouldn't have Aldi on the panel. I know I
Related it before anything happens. It's okay
Big deal
I'm fine being gang, I'm fine.
Look, I'm, look, I've been here for two minutes,
I've already 24 people in the chat.
Okay, Christine, love you.
Sorry about that, guys.
I know, guys, we're just having a time to try to have fun.
But you guys have to be, like, make it.
You guys have to try to ruin everything.
See everyone's friendly in here
Nice China, yeah
I feel like having anyone up yet. I don't know no guys
I still have my drinks.
You can drink it, energy drink, kind of warm, I guess.
Hi guys.
Hi, Sassie.
Jamie.
I know, well, Christine,
it's like, do you want to be a mod?
Because I've asked you, like, you know,
and you said no, but, you know, if you can,
you can help, I know you're always watching.
I understand it's a hard job
Yeah, thank you. I mean, oh shit. What's this? What am I saying? Oh cheese here. Here that are cheese
She's all she's thought the sandwich
Yeah, this is always watching
Okay, just remember you can get a second of these how the ones you don't actually care about your well-being. Thank you. Okay. Okay. I know
Gonna help me out
Okay, Christine. Yes, okay
That is what you'd be able to
And they're always looking out for the chat
If I can also post my link, if I can post my link, yeah.
Okay.
Let me see what else, let me see.
Top fans.
Got 30 Diamond, number two.
Jamie's Cowboys, number three.
Daisy May, 64.
I'm sorry, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just
Yes, I was kind of have to be a little bit less lenient, but if you are if you would like to be a mod
You know, I'll consider you just let me
Let me think about it for a little bit and it kind of proved to me that
You're on the side of the channel
Again have like mods on dead dead is or like after certain people or that kind of thing
Hi, babe
It's Lenore a little bit on the North where
How are we doing in chat today, hi babe
Yeah, yeah, thanks Lenore. Where's Rudy? Rudy's in the kitchen. He likes to sit in the kitchen
a nice little cool place in there.
Thank you, Sassie, for posting the rules.
Thank you, guys.
It's gonna be,
hey, easy.
You always win sexy Abe, who's sexy Abe?
Who, do I know you?
Mods take a sexy a I can check about
First another channel
It's a little boxing
They're new
Hey, the Norho knows looking at me. She's playing down here
Oh my gosh, straight.
So I'll give this a back go out of the ball.
It's kind of like.
Thank you, Jeff.
Yeah, that's pretty great headphones.
There's a lot of new chatters.
Yeah, everyone's chat out where you're from.
How'd you find the channel?
You know, if you'd like to come on the panel,
I need you to post my link.
We'll see if it works a little bit better this time.
I don't know people having trouble people behave themselves we see
I'll say to try to bring the try to bring the drama though here
We have sassy number one I love the ratings teams were three
Okay, hey, man, thank you for being here. Love ya
No, what are you trying to win
We're trying to win guys
On a competition. Oh
Thank you, Jamie. What a nice message
We beta as board beta really beta. I always said better. I'm gonna have a good evening
Dance laughing a lot of emojis
Hearts one
You smiley faces you party you shop
Yeah, you can see that
Yeah, I'm getting a really cool nail cleaning kit had all these scrapers. I'll be able to scrape
All the crap my nail looks so great. There's about 10 bucks
T-Mail
Can you share your wrench? I don't know what that means
Share your wrench. I don't know it's a new thing
Put a card for the chat. Okay, let's do that for the chat.
Okay chat.
Okay, where we got here?
Okay, we got this knight of swords
Knight of swords. Oh, this guy's smooth. He's an airside or maybe romantic really good with words
He cut people down. He's the knight of spears. You know swords
Who is this man? Do you guys know this man?
It says
He's like the queen of hearts do to pull card soldiers the night of spirits is always ready for action
He bravely charges forward to meet challenges head on if you ever feel fascinating or wondering when the time will be to make
Your next move. This is your scientist square your shoulders. Hold your head high at act now
So maybe it's time to go into something, you know, hey camera action bureau
Hello, thank you for being a member Samantha. Thank you for being a member so many great members Christine
Thank you so much for donating the membership last year. We had I donated ship Christine donated a membership
Thank you so much. We had a lot of memberships Lord Vader. What's up guys? I pinned the link guess the link is pins
Uh, I don't know. I need to put some things. Jamie's cowboy is here. Yeah, we have lovely days
Please um, thank you. What would you like? What would it put it? Would you want to share it with Jamie who you're talking about?
I'll pull some more cards for you
So that's what we have for the chat. Oh, we have the seven of
panicles
There are a lot of pinnacles, something is growing, something is growing, there may be something that is not like the others in this situation.
There are a lot of pinnacles, but something has been growing.
It says, seven of hedgehogs shows you're working hard and planning carefully to set yourself up for the future.
Making decisions with long-term focus should be your goal.
Now, instinct gratification is fleeting.
Focus on creating solid foundations for future success.
Isn't that great?
Yeah, we should all have solid foundations instead of these fleeting things.
Finally, we have the page of flowers.
Page of flowers.
Those are the young flowers, right?
How the flowers are I think
The ones the page of flowers says page of flowers represent sweet social person
Optimistic eager to learn about and explore new things
Page of flowers the well-liked person who makes friends easily
Dreaming brainstorming and really embracing your imagination
Will benefit you now write down all your ideas and dreams eventually
do we find them and they'll become the foundations of your goals and future?
So I don't know if you know that person with the page or yeah, but
maybe just take the energy hey ninja with the pencil take some of the energy of that
and uh use it for yourself you know because there's a you know that's the energy of
you know the beginning of inspiration about something you know so go in and
See where it takes you
Hey everybody, how are we doing? I don't know. I need to put this beer in the fridge. I'll see if there's a cold beer in the fridge
I don't think there is I have some energy drinks to
Take in the fridge
Hi, Rudy.
Okay, I'll start with that. Oh, how are we doing guys?
Whoo, yes, I'm getting a really cool nails nail nail set has a bunch of nail tools
I still go to like clean up my nails. I just been disgusting lately. I'm so sorry. I mean, it's just like gross
Even I even I'm like, oh my god, clean your nails. I will I will
Maybe you have to admit also this bike the bike has got my nails kind of dirty because it keeps like leaving a lock on
Then driving away with the lock on and I'd like dig through the tires
How are you guys doing? Yeah, I definitely need that, huh? I got that on Timu though Timu
Yeah
Mmm. Hope you guys are doing good tonight. Well, okay bottom stuff. Oh, yeah, this is I just been it's been open in the fridge for a couple days
It's not terrible it's really flat oh
Not good. I don't think I'll drink any more of it. Oh
Not like making that face. Oh
Don't taste for you
Not moldy vases to date
Oh, it's pretty good when it's fresh though. I mean, I'm not gonna be getting more of that. I'm just gonna get one
And it's okay, I see smoke in the stick back. I mean everything I do is like getting me sick
The bomb hits of tobacco because of out of cigarettes and then that the vape
That alcohol
You're going a few minutes. Hey, how are you? Oh, here's Trixie. Hi, Mr. Trix
I don't know. What do you guys feel like doing? I think we'll have a fun night but early
Maybe head for the store. Let me see with my phone charge. Of course not. Now it's dead. Okay
All right, where are you going? Hey little buddy
Hi little buddy
No, we don't want to join the channel.
Hi.
Hi, babe.
Oh, you're looking my nose.
You're looking my nose. Oh, you're looking my forehead.
That's sweetheart.
Give me kisses
Right TV
You know it's outside the noise we kiss
Hey guys
This you do yeah, it takes beautiful. Yeah, can you can you kiss this if you go to the good sir?
Loves you tonight
It's Friday night and the mood is right
I'm gonna have some fun show you how it's done TTI. Yeah, I need to charge my phone.
I'll use like at least 25%. It is a fast charging phone.
Yeah.
I'm looking forward to today. Let me see. Can you escape from your house today?
I came back 15 minutes later, started raiding. Oh, yeah.
They don't like that rain.
Well, my cats will be outside looking at the cats will come on soak you wet some of the cats like water more than others
Up up hey, there's Lola
Lola Lola came in
Oh, yeah, that wasn't a very good sip of alcohol
Hello guide de sapiens
How are you? Hello everybody
Welcome to the show. Hope you have fun in the show. The show's about having a good time
Many good people awesome people like Jamie's cowboys things that is sassy scarlet
An angel with a pencil guy de sapiens the dog looks like the ladies animal now
Yeah, are you pretty lazy these cats are pretty lazy. You're pretty lazy. Are you pretty lazy?
Now you're on tv. You're on tv. Hi, spunky. Here's Lola. I don't know if it's Lola.
Oh, it's right here in the north of here. Hello again.
Damn, just thinking of what we should do. Probably go to the, go a few minutes.
They do have these up what he's called backwoods. I don't know if they're just raps or they're actually cigars or something
I don't know maybe I should try them
Couple of those instead of cigarettes. I'm getting I don't know if they're just tapers though
Anyone know backwards
Hi guys
So how's it has it been on YouTube lately? I know how the streets been has it been weird has it been
Interesting. I just know that it's kind of turning a little bit weird. Oh babe
There's gonna be a little bit. Oh, no, no, no, no, no the fight with tricks is getting a little bit weird on their panels and stuff
Hey, I mean I still go but
my babe
Weirdness some other chance. I'm just these slanders. Hi. This is Miss Lola. Hi Lola
You're kissing me to you tricks because no one knows not what was gonna come kiss me. We love kissing from you. I
Can have kisses from you too. I love you
My baby. She's so beautiful
Are you a beautiful cat? You're a beautiful cat. Oh, I love you. I love you. Love you. Love you. I love you. Oh
You're so sweet
Yeah, she's very sweet. The energies have been insane lately. Yeah, how do you felt it?
you know, I think it's just like, you know, the summer souls, it's like the hottest day of the year, or like, you know, at least the sun's out the longest, and so it's, you know, this intense solar energy kind of infusions, and then, you know, we, like, live off that, that burst until the fall, until the fall, and then it kind of slows down.
We ensure it goes to the opposite.
Yeah.
But you know what we can get through these
These periods
Appreciate appreciate the moment we have we're here. We're not you know, but I think most of us are in our right minds
Are you know able to walk and talk and communicate right speak?
Share I know we still have a lot of abilities
No, don't be afraid of what's happening in the world. Oh
It's gonna happen in the future. You know, just live in the moment
As you come to any obstacle you'll be able to face in the obstacle
It's been beautiful distractions. Yes
Crazy chas help you so much. Well, that's good. Yeah, if you can like you can like
Get through my chas you can survive
You know any you kind of hazing there's just so much hazing in it. Prepare your cards today
Today I thought I got your card. Well, I'll get up and do it
Jamie wants a daily card. I'll pull a card every day
Jamie we got oh
King of cups it's got the little door knob
Okay, he's kind of friendly or the friend he was kind of a friendly doorknob. He just needed the key but
Yeah, they have the king of cups. This is the king of teacups with his that's a kind carry paternal figure
He tries his very best when it his guidance is soft
You're feeling overwhelmed by a challenge or conundrum the king of teacups suggests you seek out the wise advice of someone with
Experience in these matters and your best interest at heart. That's great advice
Anybody else want a card we'll do some cards
You like that Jamie yeah
You get the door, right?
I hope you get through that door.
Spunky's next, okay? Spunky is a membership.
So, we have nine of cups. Nine of cups. Nine of cups is like, you know, really
guarding your happiness and you've got all these things making you happy already. And
you're like, you got that one more cup you want to go for. There's just one more thing you need, right?
But it says the Nine of Cuffs is its positive sign and successful outcome. Luck is on your side. Your wish has been granted.
Things are finally going your way. Stay in the present moment. You fully enjoy the ease of comfort of this wonderful time.
Okay, so that there's been a lot of success recent success and
That's always and then more cups. Okay, so now I got the four of cups. Okay, the four of cuffs
For the emperor but this four of cuffs says
You have a tough choice to make and having trouble coming to a decision
You may be feeling overwhelmed with opportunities, but unable to pursue all of them or you may be struggling to weigh one
Option against the other user intuition how make the decision
Okay, but it's just good. You know, you have a lot of cups so far. He's a lot like a lot of emotions involved
Okay, it finally up the emperor. Okay, he's with the emperor
You know this guy is the dynamic guy. He's all the way all the kings in the deck
You know, he's like also the king of hearts. He's romantic. He's also kind of like the
one that can
You know calm things down
We see Emperor says the king of hearts is a potential leader who often tries to persuade his hot-tempered wife the queen of hearts
Be reasonable and keep her cool. Have we got this yesterday? There's a lot of motions, right?
The emperor reminds our brothers a patriarch or authority figure when like the king of hearts values good sense good sense and self discipline
Okay, so I was one vice for spunky. There's one vice for spunky
advice for you is
It's a suspension because he says I don't think about the hangman before there's a hangman
But this is like a kind of like nicer wave suspension, which is like saying
You know just watch to see things from a new perspective. It says Alice's
Imagination curiosity center tumbling down the rabbit hole in an exciting top speed terby world of adventure
Suspension represents the importance of taking breaks to explore dream and see the world from new perspectives
So it's very similar to the hermit card energy. I get for you
You never got that card, but it is similar to the hermit which I think you have been getting which is like, you know
suspension and
The vet also I like how it's like, you know, this is like, you know, it's not like she's hanging
She's just like falling she's seeing her. She sees herself from a new perspective. She's seeing herself in the
Mirror like that, right?
Yeah
Anybody else who else wants a card anybody wants a card tonight?
We're just hanging out for a little bit. I might go and hop on my bike soon and go to the store again
I don't want to take another sip of these
I hear people down first.
Just someone's a card.
Okay.
Just look at the page of hedgehogs.
Okay, page of hedgehogs.
This is like a page of pentacles.
So this is like some kind of new beginning
of some kind of new venture.
And, you know, you're at the very beginning of it, and you have maybe something to learn, but...
But you will you mean I think you can grow the page of hedgehogs is eager to be
Helpful and learn new skills, but it's a bit ineffective at present opportunity is all around you now
So it's a potential for working towards some meaningful success and material stability
Explore new opportunities with common sense. It's your long-term goals in life
Okay, and so it's it's beginning of it's kind of the beginning of a venture, right?
You're gonna get it together now. Oh great
Thank you for having me
Table yeah, so I'd say a new venture. I think it might be in the beginning stages of it now
but you know look at the long-term
potentially long-term potential of it and
You know
You can do an advice card for just if you guys are sitting there. Yeah, I got this says the pair, you know, yeah
But yes, so so I think this is the lover's car, you know, and this is like, you know, we got see advice
It just worked together right starting a new job
Yeah
So I think yeah, also. Yeah, also the advice might be like, you know, you're sure that actually can you have one guy? Yes, you can guy
Okay, what do I got for guy?
Okay, we got this queen of
Panicles queen of hedgehogs. I don't know if you know this woman, you know, this woman's obviously fertile or you know has brought stuff into the world
So this is a good woman. I love to give an earth sign you're attached to or you know
It can be but usually represents, you know a woman in your life
You know abundant of pinnacles, you know cereal
This is a nurturing practical figure who likes a fulfilling life of abundance like the mother bird
She's maternal protective person. She takes pride in maintaining a comfortable home
The queen of hedgehogs advise you to stay resourceful nurturing and kind
Yes
If I some advice for you I would say
Yeah, this is a one of spears which is like the truth so like tell the truth find the truth speak the truth
or just like, you know, you have the truth, right?
Or you're trying to have a baby?
Okay.
Ha ha ha.
Well, good luck everybody, you know.
Hope you guys enjoy those readings.
At least some more people want some.
Yeah.
I meant go, hey, there's all the cats are on me.
Hey, there's Lola.
There's Lola.
If I get people I trust on the panel, I'll go take a shower and just have people I trust
on the panel bring it for a little bit, but I do want to probably go get some drinks.
It is $5.53.
Guy wants one?
Yeah.
Guy.
I'll continue.
I'll give Guy a word of advice, too.
Guy, do you want some advice?
Ooh.
Another queen.
Queen of flowers.
I don't know. I think there's these really good feminine quality, feminine fears around you that
they really want to emulate or learn something from and let help you.
There's Queen of Flowers is a social person who takes pride in her appearance and speaks her mind with elegance and authority
admired by others. She commands attention wherever she goes.
It's time to hold your head up high, put your and people's talents and skills on display and embrace the unique traits that make you who you are.
So interesting.
Yeah, I think I've been through a lot of the lot of the cards in this deck now. Oh
Here I just pulled the king of hedgehogs, I just pulled the king of hedge, king of pentacles
This might be for you or for everybody. This might be more advice for you
It's coming to your kingly, kingly
Kingly self, king of hedgehogs says
The king of hedgehogs is a masterful person who has built his success through hard work and persistence.
Take inspiration from the carpenter. He's the skills to build a restaurant where he can make his dinner dreams come true.
Set yourself up to discipline and dedication.
So I don't know, is there something you want to start like a restaurant maybe? I don't know.
That's kind of specific for the king of pentacles. You know, he's a carpenter at least.
Or whatever it is, build something of your dreams.
This is Lola.
This is pretty quiet.
OK, so maybe time to go to the store, bike lock.
Thank you.
She is too gorgeous.
OK.
Maybe I'll wait a little bit longer. It's not just 13% maybe just a little bit. She is let's see if there's more people come in
I don't know
It's fun going to the
Story yesterday. It's fun taking a bike. I mean it's a little bit of thrill
writing kind of fun
She's going around
I sold my coffee up to you
Yeah, he's amazing guys and see that's six is mom
His dog barking welcome guy
How's everyone doing
So I'm thinking they actually have this restaurant called The Habit. I'm not The Habit, it's called
Standing Room. Let me check out the menu because I might want to get some food there. I might order
some food to go. Let's take a walk. They're gonna go down there to get home.
order online
I've had some really good stuff here before though. It's really tasty. It's kind of expensive
They have a whole salmon dinner for like 22 bucks
Okay
So they have trouble parmesan fries brussel sprouts $7. I had the brussel sprouts
Okay, burgers. I can have a burger for like $11 cash burger
Danger burger spicy vinaigrette
But that's $13 and I have $22 they've sandwiched it's like I'm a buck buck
They have a bully a charlotte a K Dilla a quesadilla. It's not called the Oscar Chris
chopped soft-shell crab tie crab man. They have a sally grease roast
salmon
Fufu
I mean they're kind of expensive
What do you guys think pork belly plate $20, okay, I'm just thinking
The Oscar, it says, Trist, Topso Crab, Tie Crab Mayo.
It's a sandwich.
It looks kind of...
...bully.
Shorty, Short Rage Rib, Genghis Khan.
I have a sandwich.
I have a burger.
A cash burger.
It's time to go to the pier. I know but it's six o'clock. I think I'll make it on time make lately everything close
Let's use here for
Hello
Yeah, fish tacos, yeah.
I don't know.
I've been eating a lot lately.
Oh, oh, there I am.
Famous, famous guys.
Here we go. I love this energy. Yeah
Just some things for you you are the one
I don't know, I can't figure it out.
I figure it out.
It is music.
I'm looking for something in red.
Oh, I'm looking for something in green.
I think I knocked over the camera.
What happened?
Oh, oh, here, uh-oh.
You're the sweetest girl in the world
Okay, well, let's let's do that 20% yeah
Oh, hi, babe.
Oh
How are you guys doing?
Okay, well, I guess we'll go between percent or no
Out of the house
If it dies, I'll be home soon. Okay, but I'll do it with that.
I wish I could find a place for the happy hour or something, but...
Thank you.
What was that?
Did you see that?
It went down here.
It went down the street view.
That better sound like total ass wants to listen to it on the TV.
Okay, I'll let you honestly get back on that.
some dance, you know, to get into the library and have a library of sales there. I got a lot of useful books there.
It feels like my face almost feels...
if you guys are back, it wasn't that fun.
Okay, I'll just pull you in my bag today.
That was a good one, actually.
I think so.
Thank you, big dog. Thank you, man.
I'm turning my hat backwards.
Hello?
I feel, I feel, buddy.
Is Joe there? Did you hear me, Joe? Long time no see. Long time no see, man. Hi, Joe. How are you?
Joe, you okay? I got one question for you, psyche. Yeah, what country song is this?
I throwed out my shoulder, but I wanted that teddy bear.
I got her saying, honey, bud, little sweetie and bitch.
I ain't seen a bitch play a game all year.
If I don't get some sleep, I'm going to blather around.
Long love, buddy, said I'm getting into deep, but I love it.
I love it.
I fucking forgot the words.
Yeah, it's good to see you big dog. How are you doing? It's like cheers up big man
Okay, how are you?
I'll tell you one damn thing. You're having a good hair day shout out to that fucking hair man
About that at least I gave credit were credit still
Think it's rigorous
Hi
I'm kidding
It's a train for renaissance
Yes, a little hairy thing that walked by
That was my pubic here. Um, anyway, uh, no, I'm just because I was a cat
Well, they got three beers left, so I'm not gonna make it all night
I might be here for like if you don't mind like the next half an hour
But I don't need to be here. I really don't care about you second. I want to know how you're dealing man
Always come up here make it about myself. I'm really concerned about you buddy. I've heard I've heard horrible things
You heard horrible things about who me?
Yes
What tell me I heard you were drinking Arizona hard. Is that true? Yeah, are you actually drinking Arizona hard? Yeah
Oh my god, I'm calling the police. I'm calling the cops
Oh, I'm just kidding. I'm just saying. I knew you were a gay sucky, but you're actually drinking air in the second hard.
What? What the hell?
Oh, that's Nick getting it. Hell, yeah, look at his ass.
Look at his asses, right? I'll give him credit. I'm not looking at the actual ass, but I'll give the guy credit.
He never stops moving. He has cardio like a fucking warrior. You know his cardio is good.
You know, he's you know, he used to go under like he's actually famous. He's like he's like he's retired in the normal world
He picked his death. I think his name is he's been named Jamie Kennedy and
Nice
The comedian or whatever. Yeah, that's him. What is he doing to his leg?
Do you remember when Robert and Quivers got caught singing cocaine by Eric Klam and she's like coca-cayena, coca-cayena.
Do you remember that?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Yeah, I know you do.
You're a Hours-Therm fan.
That's one thing I know about psyche.
I'm gonna bring out the most obscure, like when Wendy the retard was bowling at that bowling alley.
And she was like, we know everything about Hours-Therm.
That's a legend, right?
That's a real fan of Hours-Therm.
Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, you guys funky, Joe?
Well, I don't, but I like to.
Hi, Joe.
How you doing, Spunky?
I'm doing good. How are you?
We were talking about Howard Stern.
You have any Howard Stern memories or any Howard Stern?
You like him?
Do you want to know something?
Yes, I do.
You know, I was talking to Psychi earlier about his love of Howard Stern.
I've never seen a single episode.
Oh, well, you would love it, I think I've listened to some
All the sexy women are coming out when I come up, you know, it's not at worst like
But go ahead go ahead spunky
Girl
That's a fruit punch one.
Those things fog me up.
Be careful.
Girl, I got three of them.
Girl, look at them titties.
You're making me jealous.
Thank you, you know.
You got three of them.
Wow.
Well, I got a deal.
It's $3 for $12.
So why would I not take advantage of that?
Because it's supposed to be $4.
Do you drink white cloth?
No, no, man. Yes, that's my stomach. Oh
Well, I I got white claw green apple. Oh shit. It's the bomb
It's like a green jolly rancher
I never drank I thought spunky. I know white claws have very low in carbs
And I thought about drinking them, but I know it sells her water and I just love drinking beer. Yeah
Good like Amy, what do you think of nine out of ten or ten out ten?
So it's probably normal people too
But your boobs are hanging out of your shirt, so you might want to pull your shirt no, they're not
No
There you go
Oh Lord, I'll show I'll be on here with my whole bra girl when you proud
It's okay
Yeah, I'll stream with my bra on
I'm kidding. No, I'm I'm the mirror.
I make a little joke and I'll be rude.
Like, we don't play no offense.
We don't got you ever have to, like, shave your tits.
Like, oh, shit, my tits are getting hairy.
I got to shave them.
Oh, no.
No, I mean, do you ever shave your hairy, do you ever shave your hairy balls?
Oh, Joe, Joe, do you shave your hairy balls?
Joe, do you pick your dingleberries out of your mouth?
Do you, do you shave your hairy old hanging balls that are wrinkly?
They're so old, like, can you throw it over your shoulder?
I know, they're wrinkly, they're just so wrinkly, they're just so wrinkly and gross.
Oh, you can't even imagine the wrinkles.
They're so wrinkly, it's like a fucking Blair Witch project.
I've seen them before though, remember oh
Yeah, we're not sent them to you. Yeah, but no when we had a freak off when we had a freak off back stage
We had a freak off back
What is it what is your do what do you what did you do back state? What did Joe do back stage?
I showed you
He showed his you know, he showed his Joe
He showed us why people call it. He's a wife. He showed me why people call him big Joe
But the big man when I a case like he gets mad when I hit on him because he knows I'm not days
Like this is not even worth my while Joe's so heterosexual
It's not even worth my time to flirt with it
But guys like Joker that are actually kind of little gay. He's like likes that, but he knows Dan
Well ain't never go throw with me put
Like you keep trying to take all my men
No
How did Joe how did Joe look was it like was it like red pubic hair?
It's like
Orange more, you know, it was gray. It was gray
It turned gray turn gray Joe. Oh my god. Yeah, he's
I am too sober for this y'all. I mean I'm too sober for this shit for this fuckery
Let me
Long balls silver from now on
The response is funny
I'm like little Wayne a little flip-flop up here in the corner
What up, Jamie flip, you know, that's the way we ball. Oh, that's Nick. I'm fucked up. I'm sorry. I know that's Nick
He always does it look at it flip it up. He's just
Having you
No, you listen he's in Texas. Oh, he looks like he's Florida Manning out there just tearing shit up
Mm-hmm. I don't know how he's working out because if it's hot in here in Cali it must be hot in Texas like I don't understand
I want to but I'll see if it works out. I just need a plane ticket
You're gonna fly Nikki out that psyche are you gonna stream from there? Yeah with a lease at least that's Lisa
I don't know if you'll have to introduce me to her next time when she's in here.
Okay, well she doesn't ever come here.
Yeah, she has her own show, she has her own show, she's a popular streamer, she's on
her, she's on right now, you can see what she looks like, Lisa Jordana, E-I-S-A, Jordana.
Yeah, Jackie, uh, Psyche has a crush on her, she will be the one woman to turn Psyche straight.
No, I'm number two.
I love you, Lenore.
You know you're my you've stolen my YouTube chat virginity. Oh my gosh, the first person. Oh my gosh. Yeah
She's got pretty eyes, too.
Bunky, I give you a lot of credit for turning your cameras.
A lot of women, I got to turn it, so I can't even look at myself,
but I give you a lot of credit for turning the cameras.
Cam up, Joe.
Cam up for us.
Yeah, Joe.
Cam up.
Stop being a bitch.
If I'm cute, stop being Cam up.
I'm not doing it for you guys.
I'm turning it off for you.
Do it.
I'm not.
You're here with two twins right now.
You're here with two twins, you know,
because apparently we're twins.
Yeah.
So I came in the chat.
And I got on camera.
People said we were.
People said we were twins.
Oh, spunky.
Spunky looks like flirty diamonds.
How does like it all the sexy women up here like what does he do? He don't even say words
He just like all of a sudden just booms bumpies up here
That's that's enough I know that's too much
You know Joe Joe already said Joe Joe you already said you wanted to do this one with anal beats and for the day
You said he was gonna pull it out with his fucking teeth
No, sir, no, sir. All right, well no sir back to you sir
Joe, you're old.
I'm old. I'm as old as you.
Joe, you don't take rejection well.
Joe, how old are you?
I'm old. I'm fucking 37 years old.
I'm 23. You're older than me.
And you look 40, first of all.
Well, I'm forty-one, so you just said I look forty, so you just said I look younger than I am. Thank you.
No, you said you're thirty-three.
I know it was a lie, dumbass. Get it?
Okay, well, see, I knew you were in your forties, see? I knew you were in your forties regardless.
Oh, that's a wig-a.
Regardless, Joe. Regardless.
Regardless, really.
The point still stands.
Oh, it stands very well you what do you think it does? I bet it does. Oh, I know it does
What
Over 29 years old definitely over 29. Are you really? Oh
Don't be a dick
I
Penile well, I don't know if that applies. I'm sorry. Sorry. I don't penile input, but
I want a girl's input, but I
Got a bottle of blue chew right next to me. You didn't do it
No, no, that's just no, I think there's a love connection between spunky and Joe
Are you are psyche? Are you reading a love connection between those two cuz I am
He's actually in the chat flirty
And he's sitting right over there
Wait, who's your boyfriend Justin Boyle?
I
Justin your girls at least she lives it Justin your girl got your back. I can respect that she got
What babe
Oh, he said oh nothing
Damn Joe got rejected again
Another one another one bites the dust
Another rejection Joe got rejected again
So he got rejected by a tranny and then you got rejected by spunky too. Wow
No, I'm ignoring that
Girl, he's in there saying he said and I quote
Talking to my boyfriend boil if you came home after a hard day's work and saw a flirty tap and spunky from the back
Would you leave or watch?
That's a fair question.
That's a fair question, whoever has it.
I like Dick.
I mean, Spooky can use the strap on, I guess, but I'm not.
I don't really like women.
Oh, my god, Christine asked if I'm trans.
I'm not trans.
I'm just accepting everyone.
That's the name.
She's jealous.
Like, God, that's kind of rude.
Spongy sir, what's up with your dots in the chat as fast Eddie?
I know they if you're like only jealous bitches are mad over pretty good
Dot hates me so much that she blocked me, but then she creates like 10 million accounts to troll me. It's really cute
When I stream so many people that say that they hate me, that they find me ugly, they
all, they all, they're in my chat whenever I stream, exactly, obviously I'm making my
own content and they're still viewing me, and it's cute, it's always the same shit,
like get a new gig, you know what I mean, like
It can't be the same, I'm just-
Oh, here's my problem, spunky.
All the transphobia that's been targeted at me has been told to me almost my whole life.
And I'm barely 23 years old.
Yeah, girl.
If you're gonna say something, let me just fucking come up with something that hasn't been told to me before.
Like, I got 23 years worth of fucking transphobia that's been said to me.
Like, be more original, please.
I live in an area that's a little bit conservative.
Oh girl, same.
I'm in Cali, but where I'm at, it's conservative still.
And guess what?
Those men are still in my DMs, those conservative men's are still in my fucking DMs, regardless
of the file.
I work as a primary care provider, like the main doctor you go to.
And I get all the LGBTQ community because everybody else sucks.
Spongy you could give me
Yeah, Joe you want to get that prostate exam in a minute, you know
Three days in a row what the fuck I'm gonna check that PSA you gonna be yelling
I
Get you
You know
Girl, I tried doing the world a favor by donating plus one today and I couldn't donate for being trans actually
Yes, because they want my doctor to sign up on my medications to prove that I'm not doing shit illegally and I'm just like
I'm not dealing with that shit like I will rather go somewhere else like I wanted to just make some quick change
You know, I wasn't drinking yet and I just was like
you know I want to do this it's good for the it's good for people and I want quick change real quick
I was gonna say that's a nice thing to do that's a yeah I wanted to do it for my like you know
I've done it before but I wanted to just do it because like I wanted money quickly because I want to buy weed but like
I can't right now
You're having the world of my way and yes
Exactly and like it was just crazy to me. So that's what I mean
I get discriminated on the daily basis like what people say to me on the internet is light work
Yeah
It's like he said to me was so rude so he said he was gonna lick your butthole even though it's hairy
So that was kind of nice of him
That's kind of nice of him to come to still eat hairy ass. I was nice of him. Oh, you got a dingleberry ass. I know it
You do don't you I'd say to show
Like that
Joe showers once a week. What do you mean?
You must be up in Dingleberry's ass all the time spunky. I guess you would know baby
Let me crack your beer. I gotta open my beers with a fucking beer opener
Wait spunky spunky. Have you ever ate ass before? No, no
Justin and I joke about this all the time. We had we met on hinge, right?
and
We are like the kinkiest most vanilla people you could ever meet. How does that?
How is that? We enjoy sex
But we ain't any nass
We ain't any nass. I ate ass once in my life actually you did. I don't do no peps
From ETC. I don't I don't know
Her night joke around a time cuz she's a ass once in her life, too
And I joke we're trying we're trying to recruit more munchers
I'm not joining the munch munch
Tomorrow looks bad and the rest of the entire like
Century looks bad, too. Okay. What about the next what about the century after the century? No
Weatherman we're tired of it. It's sunny
Joe, why are you mad?
Yeah, why are you so mad?
Joe, we're friends with you. Don't be mad.
You went from just joking around to cussing out the weather, man.
Do you know why, Flirty?
Fuck that weather, man.
I told him I had a boyfriend and he got mad.
It's okay, Joe, you know, I'm dating raging so no nobody's
Me flirty diamond you piece of shit fuck it all
That is not how raging looks first of all
No, it's not how you're not see you have not seen his dick pic Joe
You can see his face on his dick pic it's
And he doesn't look like that like people the photos that they're using a raging to make him look fat and everything through fucking editing
But he's not fat
People can make fake comments that I can like like make yeah
But I don't care channel one time
She showed a picture of a comment that raging wrote to you and it was like I don't even think I'm gay
But I'm just so in love with you. I just want to I mean that's true
He said that he's not gay
Yeah, I'm his first trans
Yeah, how about that raging has your first trans? How you feel Reggie?
You little cage. I'm your first trans to Joe
Well, hey keep it quiet
Joe, I have a video of you saying that you'll shove anal beads
Jo, don't fuck around right now.
Fuck around and find out, Jo.
Exactly.
Or the anal beef will go up to you instead.
We can fuck around.
Jo.
Justin, you tell them.
Flirty.
They picking on me up here saying I'm trans too,
because I'm being friends with you.
Yeah, I think you're a beautiful I think you're beautiful for being trans
My cities are
That's what I'm saying like people think that trans woman can't grow boobs and it's like
It's amazing. Oh, so that remember that drunk chick that was on our chat the other night like just fucking just
Which one was I up here what I wanted to say to you, honey
After you turn 40
In a million years and you need to get a mammogram, you know that right when you grow your own titties
Yeah, she bought cancer. Yeah. Yeah, you know that even though you grow them on your own you still got to check them out
Yeah, no, I know and I okay
But you know, she's a guy Spongy a guy doesn't need a mammogram. Oh, yeah, she needs a mammogram
Okay, so I have plenty of patience
No, how about you put on a bra and let's compare boobs sizes
Let's see your titties like you know, stay together like this or the more like this
Take out your shirt, Joe. Let me take out your shirt and put on a bra put on a bra for us
You want to see how nice your boots? We need to see how nice your boots are with what a bra
Put a ball for us
Yeah, put on a bra for us Joe show me yours. I'll show you mine
Cuz Joe we know you're not wearing a bra
Look at me like when I'm talking to you Harry Edward says her hands. Oh
My god, Justin is creamy his pants right now Sebastian and God he are in chat
Oh my God. Oh my God. Well, how's everyone doing? I just can't imagine getting implants
and then hating on someone that doesn't have implants. Sorry, sorry, so you're, you're
all natural. You just started taking hormones and your boobs. Yes.
Yeah, I've been on hormones for like four, I've been on hormones for four years, I've been on hormones for four years now.
I have some patients who are elderly and have been on hormones for a long time and they got some staggy old titties.
That happens to them too.
I am staying perfect for the rest of my life. I drink vampire blood.
I don't want to, I don't want to hate on you, but.
I drink vampire blood.
That's okay.
So I will never never experience this
You know what when I when I get old and my boobs go to shit for being old
That's when I'll get implants and then you know, I can compare implants with my hater down down in the chat
And now you're done now my turn to thought sponkeys trying to say that sponkeys an actual woman
And when you get older, gravity takes turns.
So you're like, don't have real to the offense already.
No, no, my my titties are fake though.
So it doesn't count.
Thank you.
Thank you, spunky.
Thank you very much.
I'm just saying it doesn't it doesn't count.
See.
They don't say.
And let's be honest, if I got my boobs done,
I would get a bigger size.
Why would I have this?
Why would I get.
I had C's and I went to a double D.
I have a D need but they're too big. I literally I literally have a D actually
Now I'm a D cup and I have a D. Yeah
D cup and you have a D you're double D's
Double D's but good
Reggie D man, what did you watch with Reggie D yesterday?
What movie did you watch?
We watched Titanic 666 on TV.
Oh, okay.
That was what I was watching.
And yesterday we watched Sinners.
What's Sinners?
And we watched Norbit.
When you were watching the movies, did you guys get naked and stuff?
No.
We just fucking, we just FaceTime and watch a movie.
I
Do you have a time for like fun
What do you do, what do you do when you?
You know
We don't have some fun. What do you do? Well when we have some fun. That's I start doing psyche. See look
I start going like this, you know. Oh my god. Oh, yeah
Hey, you know
Know I'm wearing a crop top. It's like I really gotta go
You know
That's how I go from here
It's just do you too much at once and you got you got to build up that tension psyche, you know
Everybody
It may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it may be too long, it
it's a little bit but it's
How wonderful life is, while Spongebob is in the world.
Josh is just in love with me.
I think from 5 a.m. I just want to watch like
Sebastian is a trooper say you know Sebastian was on your channel talking on his own
to himself
Yeah, or five hours
I mean, I woke up I woke up at like seven of the warrior. Yeah, he was still talking it. I was I listened to
He wasn't being bad, but then people were saying always be controversial
No, no, he was being a good boy. He really was Sebastian is a very good boy
He really was he didn't say one plus word the entire time not one
Yeah, the controversy is you know, like we're being controversial right now
You know, it's like whatever
Who's
Dog how about me Bersh UJ dogs happy you broke up with baby would you say
Spunky lick them again
Just don't buy up. Oh, she's broke. She fell off
I think she realized it was her mic that was fucking ruining everything
It was okay. Let's have a little look at this. Oh
You're talking to yourself, I know you're talking to people watching but I just mean like nobody else was on panel with you
That's all I wasn't picking on you babe
Yeah, you got Robo voice
Yeah, it's like your mic is like breaking up
Inside if you can
Go inside in the fireplace
Let me grab my drink I got some you can grab
I bet you do Joe.
Leave my girl alone.
Joe, no.
You took your head off.
I would have cried.
I really would have cried.
Don't cry.
I don't want to pick on you, but I don't see a resemblance, oh, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday,
Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday, Saturday,
Oh, but Joe, I want to mess up Mike. Joe, you need to fix your mic because you're the one that
Is it mine?
Is that mine?
I don't have a mustache like what the fuck?
I was like, I got this and like, like rocker lips.
No, no, we have this little like a thing on our face.
Do you see it?
Yeah, that's not what happens with people.
But like, yeah, but that's why I think we look alike or why
people say we look alike.
Otherwise I've been studying we got nothing
Whiskers, that's why I think you look like you both have a little whiskers. Let's get you used to your mom's whiskers on your tit like leave me alone
That's that's too far that is too far
That's total opposite, but I said it
Fair enough you got me
How are we doing? Anyone want to come up? Is this easy? Are you okay?
Yeah, Sebastian, Gotti, where are you?
Joe, can you fix your mic? Can you fix your mic, Joe?
Fuck you.
I'm being serious. Fix your mic, because you're the only one that I hear it.
Yes, you're the only one that has any time you talk, I hear issues.
You can talk, I hear the issues.
If Spike says, Joe, go fix your mic, I'll leave it and gladly fix my mic.
Yeah, I'll try to fix it.
Like, he's the only one that can't hear properly, actually.
I can hear spunky.
I can even hear Nick perfectly.
All right, let me come back, let me come back though.
Just give me a chance to come back, let me fix it.
All right, make your lips again, and I'll be back.
No, make your lips right now, Smunky.
Oh, all right, I'll be back.
I'm not your base, Joe.
Doesn't it sound, my mic sounds fine, Flirty.
You're trying to make me happy.
No, yours is fucked up too.
You and Flirty were sounding bad,
but Flirty's fine now that she went inside.
Oh, now she's fine. Okay. I've been fine. Well, she's happy. Exactly. I've been fine Joe you
Never seen a girl with a beer belly
You literally are dating a girl with a beer belly that visits you every night. That's all I'm not dating it
I'm actually saying I'm not dating anyone. If you think I'm being somebody that's on you
I'm not dating anyone. You know you're dating that one you're dating that one lady that always thinks I with you
No, her name's Kim. She's one of my best friends. No, you're dating
Do it again do it again
Again do it again do it do it do it do it do it
On the big screen, what are you doing? I can't even see her
What are you trying to do now?
That's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to say, that's all he came up to
Joe you'll still slide them through back and forth between them. You know, you would
Why is my head purple?
You're not black you're not black
You're not black
You know what? I actually am black. So you know what fuck you know, they're not Joe. You're the most honky
Like you're literally the most honking ass in the world.
Let's take a post to my only hands.
Oh my God.
Fun shirt. That's what I that's what made me talk about it a little roughly shoulders like
Huge what do you fucking George Washington's fucking slave with your little roughly clothes?
This is designer don't hate on it
I'm not hating on it.
The thing I'm saying is like in the 1700s,
they wore roughly shoulders.
So like you're closed like 200 years out of style.
That's what I'm saying.
My plants all at work are old people, so.
Gotta make them happy.
I don't know, hey.
You gotta do what you gotta do, I guess, baby.
Gotti, that's offensive.
God, what did he say?
Let me see what he said.
He said.
He's my son.
I met Mongo and he's a pair of Goddys.
Mongo is my, what he calls my son.
Goddys, Goddys.
You be, go Goddys.
Goddys.
Don't do it again.
That's a new low.
That is.
How low can you go, Goddys?
What is it?
Come on.
You're better than that, Goddys.
At least I hope you are.
Well, what did you know? What are you worried about? What would you do?
God is being really rude in the chat room. I
Can't hear you babe. Oh don't just suck a dick. Oh, there you go. Tell him to suck a dick
You know I have 12 inches
Okay, give me one second, okay?
Okay, one second. One sec. No I'm putting it back. There you go. See, look, suck it.
There you go. I don't know if that's the last one.
Oh my gosh.
And at least because they're natural,
they're real women, so they're natural.
Be nice, they're not natural.
Oh, they're not natural actually
You think she's told you they're implants?
Yeah, they're implants, I'm all fucked up
There's nothing wrong with her implants
See, her implants aren't botched, so they look good
Yeah, they're not, I look like a
I'm just saying, I will feel
I got a fine-sized dick
But I will feel so weird getting a dick implant
Look, they
You must feel so inadequate
They don't look fake, like they look like
No, they don't look fake at all
They don't fucking make a fool of me
So like I'll be right back. I need a glass of milk all of a sudden. Talk to you in a second. I
Need a big glass of milk
Yeah, Justin I'm packing everybody knows I'm packing I'm not I just sprouted mine a few weeks ago, but I'm trying
Okay, should I have a tropical punch or should I have an orange blast orange blast? Yeah, I want to go to I want to blast to Mars
You're gone
Go to boy, I'm going to go to Uranus actually I want to go to sponky's Uranus. Hello anybody there a sponky's Uranus
Who was on the chat that said Uranus and I about died
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
He's being too quiet. Go ahead ladies. I'll suck your dick from the back
Thank you. I actually I appreciate that if actually probably feel good. Go ahead get down
Yeah, it's funky you're gonna suck it from the front I got it from the back to the front
No, the orange juice the orange juice is too strong for me cuz I the
I kind of just hit me just now the fruit and I tried drinking the orange and like if I have it, I feel like I'm gonna gag
No, what are you talking about undo and shoe my hair he's talking she's talking I mean
I grow up
Grow the hell up 30
I
No, no, honky, I mean, I guess you could say...
Oh, Sebastian, when women undo their hair when it's up, it is not as beautiful as in
the movies.
Florida, tell them.
My hair is naturally beautiful, so...
It's not.
It's...
I'm kidding.
My hair fucking is too much effort.
I got textured fucking hair to the max.
It's not good.
But if I would
In fact us like as my tears well everybody except for that guy little flip for whatever his name is everybody here is good
You mean Nikki?
What even happened to Nikki?
Is that Nick Johnson?
You didn't know you didn't even know that was Nick Johnson. Wow
Stopping racist
You're racist Joe real question
I don't see an infrared
Did flip break his neck doing like a trick and we didn't notice because the camera has turned blue. Oh, no, there he is
There he is. Oh my god. He's alive pretty sure he broke his spine
Yeah, I was worried. I was worried that he hurt himself. We didn't notice and then like it got dark and he's just out there dead
Bucky, look at me. So I give you don't mind if you don't mind
Why look how I got to open this like I
Clicked the beer bottle and then
Bunky, you know, I thought but once
Nick Nick
You're a lucky girl. Yeah, he sent me his buttons
I was just like oh
Was it Harry? No, his butt is really smooth actually. I think I think he's I think he shaves it
I think he shaves his butt. I want him in front. Sorry, Nick
No, just naturally smooth it happens
So, yeah, thank you. We all see Nikki's Nikki's
shaven, but
You know, you're not special.
You're not getting the bear and the bear witch project.
That's what it looked like.
Look, Joe, and this Joe, in this moment, you're not special.
I mean, you are.
You are special ad.
But in this moment, you're not special.
Goddy, I got an art pad with your name on it.
What do you need?
It's a Jardien.
Some Mozambique.
Some Manjaro.
Hey, Sponky, I got two s chicks with your name written all over them.
What?
Oh, honey.
I
Joe
Joe do you like to get pegged it sounds like it
Conversation or no Joe do you get pegged actually?
Joe of course, I don't like to get pegged
I love it, I never fucking you were you're a weirdo flirty diamond. You like you said you love it
Like I don't like to come out. I'm not doing that. You can't that's all you spunky
Man like
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, I slapped my boyfriend's butt.
You're fucking eyes off my ass, funky.
I'll slap my boyfriend's butt, like, whenever I, I mean,
it's funny you seen a guy's reaction
when you slapped their butt.
You never slept his butt before
No, never never you are vanilla you're in a half
Guy oh, that's right. Florida diamond never slapped her as that would be weird if learning slabbed your ass like my
Yes pants on I've slapped his ass
That's what I mean, not bare ass cheeks, oh god no.
That's not his last bare ass cheeks.
No, no, I'm not talking about the difference.
Yeah, I'm not talking about the bare ass cheeks.
I'm just talking like he's standing there in the kitchen making something.
You just run up on him, you go like, boom.
So, Lou Levy's standing there in the kitchen, I am going in for straight balls.
You're not going to find her.
Joe
I'll shut my whole fist up your fucking ass Joe
I'll go. I'm going to please
Dick so I can show my dick in Joe's mouth to shut him up
These two women like what the fuck is going on here?
But he was just like, there's no help.
There's no saving you, you're done.
Oh my god.
There's no saving, he's done.
I'm done, guys.
Nice to meet you, but I'm done.
Joe, no.
We were just fucking with you.
Oh, I wasn't.
Stop it.
I know it was funny.
Oh, you know, Flirty wasn't.
Flirty wasn't.
Flirty was actually serious.
Yeah, I'll fuck, you know, we'll have a ditty party.
Just calm down a little bit, please.
Let me know where to send the baby oil.
Oh, you need to send it to Psyche's house, Psyche has peaches.
Yeah, like Psyche needs more baby oil, and you know he has 19 bottles in his house.
Oh my god.
Oh god, this is god this really a whole a whole churn. This just went a whole a whole churn just now
No, this is what I'm talking about beatboxes to Joe getting tacked team
Why are people in the chat say mango, what is that?
Oh, they're sort of tagging your child now. That's so fucked up. Yeah, it's okay
I can't see myself. Wait, let me see. Okay. My my thing is half black one second
Do you know the guy Justin? It's at Mongo. You know what his nickname is his nickname is faggot. You ever heard that?
Hey, go to fucking attack my friend squirmy or whatever the fuck her name is
Squirty?
Squirty or spunky?
Maybe Joe does know me!
Half my screen was black for some reason. I don't why streamer does that to me
Yeah, so well, you know the only thing I saw that was half black was Barry's penis
Fake photo he's taking a fake. No, that was real. Oh my god
Even if it was fake who sends people fake dick pictures
Barry you're a fucking weirdo Joe. I'll send you a dick pic
I don't you know what you're already weirdo sample matter
But if Barry send the people fake their pictures like I always thought Barry was kind of cool
But man, he's Joe Barry has saying to you know that
Barry saying to me before oh
You know what I'm gonna sing to you right now. I got 12 words. I'm feeling like a freak on a leash
No, Barry Barry was thinking sometimes he feels like people are watching me
It was a real man judge Goddy for a moment. He said some really fucked up shit. What did Goddy say?
Let me see what he said. Let me read the comments. He said a chosen boy
That's chosen boy. Don't see that bad chosen boy. What's wrong with that chosen boy?
I would have made him sleep with Rocky's body for a month. So my son
My son got high and fell asleep. Okay?
We live in the desert
And he let the dogs out and let them back let some of them back in but didn't check for the baby
Here's only a like a little a little tiny Pomeranian dog
He left him out there for hours and hours the dog passed. I'm listening baby. I'm listening
He passed away
It was fucking awful, that's how my week has been so I came home discovered the I'm like feeding everybody and come home
I'm feeding everyone. I'm like, where's my baby?
Your dog passed away within the last couple days. So you didn't even tell us
No, I didn't tell y'all, so I didn't want to be picked on.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, he was a good boy.
I remember Raven, not to make it about me, but I remember losing Raven, so I could know
what she's going through.
I wish you would have told him.
He's a good boy.
Now, I...
Well, he was a good boy.
He was a good boy.
Yeah, he was a good boy.
But, uh, so...
Gotti, like, I blame my son, everybody blames my son, you know, so Gotti's over there like
I would have made him sleep with the body.
Geez, I mean, on the lighter now, I'll put Joe down.
I
Vote you have Joe put down
I know you put the needle I know you put that needle to kill me
I know I'm sorry, I tried to make you laugh because I was really sad.
Me and Plurty, we're trying to make you laugh because we care about you.
We were just making you laugh because we care about you sweetheart.
That's what we were doing.
I think Justin just placed in his pants and we made her laugh.
Oh my God.
What the fuck?
At least we made her feel better clarity. We made her laugh, right?
Joe, you still haven't put a bra on for us.
We asked you to put on a bra 10 minutes ago.
Yeah, I want to put a bra on, dude.
Why don't you put a bra on?
My bra's fucking dirty.
Show the bra strap.
Look, it's pink.
Wow, I've never seen a guy wear a bra before until tonight
And I'm wearing pink and I'm wearing a pink thong
Look at mine. I got a fucking bra to say no you don't okay lift up your whole bra
It's not against I mean lift up your whole shirt
Wow, yeah, I actually flashed a panel you made a flash like these panel with yes
Let's see let's see them big old boobies
These big there these are like these are like
Always ask good women or a man, what are your nipples on a scale of coins, like a penny
a dime?
Yeah, I'm gonna say you got pancake nips.
I'm feeling pancake nip energy all over the channel right now.
Yeah, you know what, you might be feeling right.
His nipples are bright pink, like a salmon.
He's got some fat ass pancake nipple boobies.
Don't do it.
Yeah, I want to see.
Bring him out.
You got some hairy boobs, by the way, Joe.
He's got pancake nips, that's his problem.
And his boobs are hairy.
Yep, hairy pancake nips.
Joe, you got to change your screen name.
You're hairy pancake nips from now on.
You ladies are fucking freaks on a leash Harry nipples
Oh my god, oh my god
He got silver dollars somebody said damn that's that's actually kind of sexy
Joe
I'm gonna say you hit on my mom. This is I don't even know what I was gonna tell you actually I forgot
This was for Psyche. I've never talked to Psyche. I joined the talk to Psyche, but I've never talked to him
And then you start talking to Spunky and I
You completely abandoned Psyche and that's why he's fucking sitting in the corner watching porn
He's actually ordering fish tacos to be honest, I feel like how much fucking gay porn can you watch him one night?
It's like like really without getting a boner
Weirdo, he likes edgy
No, do you like edgy?
I like edgy too. I like no do you like edgy?
Oh edgy like when you jerk off for nine hours without coming. Oh, yeah, I don't like it. I love it
I'm actually I'm actually 42 hours into edgy right now. I'm actually 40 hours in
So what?
Sebastian was doing that this morning on panel for four and a half hours
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much. Oh my god
I was on a joke, maybe I mean edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, edging, ed
I guess it's all about you. I just want to see them
Revolts on my comment, but you want to see what?
You want to see my fucking balls? Is that what you want to say? You know, well, Joe, I've already seen your balls
That's what you want to fucking see. You're gonna fucking see it. You know, I already seen old man balls. It's okay
No, hold on one second. You're gonna see it again
You going to lift up your ankles like you're going to show me your socks and I can see your balls at the same time.
I can't even see.
He's looking at me.
What?
Oh, shit.
Is he showing balls?
What the fuck was that?
That was it.
It was moving around.
It was like really worked up.
It was waving high.
That was your fingers.
Let go of this, buddy.
That was your fingers you fucking you scared it was a finger now you're right
It had a I was scared for a second. I was genuinely scared. I was like, what the fuck
Oh my
Like my dick
Would you have a dick so you have a dick so you're admitting it so now you're fucking admit you have a dick
Well, there every other day you say you have tits now the day you have a dick you want to get sucked
No, I have a princess one
He said Justin should marry me. I have a princess one
I have a princess wand
She a woman she was I have a princess one Joe. I have a magical princess wand
Oh, wow. Yeah, it's magic
My brother psyche, I think he's like a breeze like a sister
Yeah, what are you doing? What were you doing back there? I don't know
Be a grub-hub. Oh
And I'd say sometimes when I get drunk, I just read like a like a menu and I'm like, oh that sounds good
That looks good. I just read it like oh, I love to eat that. I love to eat that
I just never
Joe, Joe you are giving me a flashback
It was the night I tried to talk to you buddy. I was drunk and I was like, oh, come on not my stupid camera
I'd love to eat that.
Yeah, that's what I do.
I could just go for that tonight.
I'll just fucking do it.
Oh, that'd be so good.
I'm like, I ain't gonna fucking pay my money.
Yeah, you don't care.
I'm gonna make tomorrow a lot more.
Fucking sounds good.
Sounds good.
I'd love reading the menu.
Give it to me.
God, Mike, what are you, what are you,
Hulk eyes?
What are you looking at?
Fucking Hulk-eyed motherfucker.
All I know is I heard spunky say give it to me when I joined. Oh
Well, Joe is going on about like give it to me. Are you gonna take my man?
We're about to scroll up
Yeah, we know we're fighting now my man is 10 feet away from me
If we're fighting you're trying to take Joe for me talk to your man if he's ten feet away for you
Let me fucking talk to him. Let me talk to him right now. Just say hi
What just Joe doesn't leave your hair. Oh, I'm here. Yeah, I'm just chilling. Yo, Justin. No offense
I know it's your girl and I won't be rude to you
But if it wasn't your girl, I'll flip her up and down like a pancake and eat her all night long with sir
Understand
I just want Justin to know he's a lucky man. What is wrong with you Joe?
What is wrong with you Joe you
Make me
Oh, thank you. I can I'll show that fucking eyeliner up your fucking nostrils. This is lip gloss
I don't care what it is. It's going up. It goes up the ass every time so watch out
Like a little lip gloss on it, I mean I've been told my ass is magical
Oh, yeah, why who by who Sam man?
By Gotti
I actually haven't told that my ass tastes really good like I've been told it tastes good actually. So got it
The guy that said that also says shoo loo loo loo loo. No
Joe Joe, I'll give you my Twitter link Joe
Thank you. I can't wait to click it
Okay, put your number backstage and we'll text
I'm actually like my number. I don't want to talk to you. Why don't you want to talk to me, Joe? I want to be friends
Well, I don't know
Why can't we be friends Joe?
You're right, clarity. Why can't we be friends Joe?
You're not lying anymore that you're not a guy. I'm not trying to bring up your shit
But you're not lying and saying you're a woman. That's one thing I don't fuck with. I mean, I'm not lying exactly
I am a form of a woman. So I'm not lying
If I ever saw your ass and you lied and I was drunk and you told me to a hotel room and I found that you're a guy
I would throw you into a fucking river and you never hear
So you would have put me around and you would lie and say you're a woman
No, you would have a woman spunky. I could tell right now. You know
But but
Just hear the other side. What's the but the but is Justin. How much of a man am I?
more than most men
how much of a man is Justin?
100% he's the most manly man I've ever met
Joe you would have flipped
no Joe you would have flipped me around
and you would have ate my ass regardless
you know one thing that's never going to happen
I don't want to see your man ass
and I'm definitely not going to eat it
Joe you literally said you're going to shove
you said you're going to shove 30
and 30 fucking anal beats up me
Now it's Mario single and I'm not just like Justin but Justin wasn't there and spunky
Have fun in vietnam with gaudi tell who
Joe I heard that her tell Joe something. What would you want to say boy? Have fun in Vietnam a guy?
Spunky look up
Spunky click on the link that I just put backstage. Oh, yeah, let's see, baby
No, what is it? Why is the brand new iPad? What am I getting into it's on YouTube?
She's gonna hear the truth about you Joe. She's gonna hear the truth about you Joe. Ah, it's me
Is it me like I love you flirty psych? What's wrong with you, man? Tell me what I'm looking at
She's
I loved her
Spongebob herself backstage you didn't see what video it is
They're well said well said buddy
I hope you can hear the audio, did you hear it, did you hear what he told me?
I saw what he told you. What did I say? I didn't hear it, but can I at least hear what I think I heard?
Listen, I don't kiss and tell. Hey, don't play it. I can't hear it. You can play it again,
but you can't hear it on the panel. You can just tell me what I said or I guess not. Something
Uh, a foot long of anal bees that you'd suck them out of them.
Oh, fuck God, a foot long Jesus.
How big somebody is?
A foot long, or either it's at a fire hose full.
I couldn't really tell because it was breaking up.
Yeah, the stick in the anal bee would be fine.
Like a foot long anal bee.
Wait, we can't see you right now.
Your screen is black.
Sorry, I'm still looking at Joe on that thing.
I don't know how to get back
You click on the tabs button and then yeah, there you are you see what you'll have
You see what he said to me spunky. I saw girl and you see what he's gotta say now
That's what I say you're like that was that was not edited you can tell it wasn't
Can you imagine what you're saying to me?
I just want to know why like, like,
tries to get like, Jonathan Taylor Thomas.
That's not fair, you like.
Jonathan Taylor Thomas, what are we in the fucking 1998?
Yeah, what do you think you are, Psyche?
You're not fucking homophobic.
Get a haircut, asshole.
Lurdy do you have any idea who Jonathan Taylor Thomas is no good
You you you a baby you're not supposed to but Joe Jesus, how old are you?
45 band whoever said that's like being whoever said that
So, you know who's mouth that came out of Joe you're trying to tell me I'm older than you I
Am 30 I'm out of day over 39 years old. No, you're Joe. You literally admitted to being your 40s like 20 minutes ago
Yeah, like what do you mean?
day bad day
but
Well, Psych is so in his gay porn, he won't even fucking listen to us, God, Psych made
that change to us.
You know what I wish I could do to Psych?
Right now I wish I could just come up, like, boop, and get out.
Psych, what restaurant are you looking at?
Like, you've been contemplating on what you're looking at.
I'm looking on door dash now. I'm looking for a deal. Like I'm looking it's like
What about subway I know subway has good deals
You eat too much seafood so you need to start eating like
Oh
My god, I love shrimp Alfredo. It was really good. Oh my god, I love chicken parmesan
Okay, I need to tell you a funny story. So like
My ex-boyfriend's name is Alfredo and like he would piss me off
I would come if he would call me shrimp Alfredo. Actually, I would call him shrimp Alfredo
I knew that was what's coming next. I knew you're gonna call him shrimp outbreak
Of course cuz he would piss me off like when he would piss me up
I'll be like you're fucking shrimp all frayed on you, but what do you mean? I'm like the fuck do you think I mean?
That's fucking awesome
Yeah, but that's what caused my permanent eyebrow scar, but you know
You are you ahead
Girl, I've been through a lot like I'm down sponky
It was
Not let's not try to trauma dump, but I'm just saying like it was girl
Yeah, I didn't think you're a bitchy and I'm just saying like that sucks. I'm sorry
It's all good. I mean I'm healing from it and that's why I make my jokie jokes
Justin beats me, too. I'm actually in a basement right now.
The only thing that he beats is that pussy.
Let's be honest.
I can't be a lesbian. I don't like females.
I find girls pretty.
I find them pretty, too, but then they open their mouth.
Right, I mean I've kissed a girl once when I was drunk, but like I don't think that counts cuz I was drunk
You know
You'd kiss me. I know you would girl
I would kiss you in front of Joe and then in front of your boyfriend. Yeah, they'd love it and
Then in front of psyche cuz we need we need to turn psyche straight
Thank you
Thank you. If we wanted to do a threesome me you and flurry diamond would you participate?
Is Justin be there or no?
No Justin he would know he'll be sitting down watching us. Thank you. Thank you
But if he would join you do it
If you join Justin, have you seen Justin? He's actually cute. No, I haven't actually seen him
Oh my god, my black he black. He looks like a fucking skinhead. He like I was about to say he sounds white
He's so white like
By the way, if you would like to know just it looks like because he won't join cam
Take off all my makeup and take off all my hair. I'm not Justin. It's getting hot
Face to your brother, okay
Brother and sister it's really disgusting
She's he looked worried. She said Joe. No you implied it Joe. You're the sickle that implied it
You didn't let her see
Yeah, what is wrong with Joe? I'm kicking you off the panel like we got to be we got to be brother and sister
I'm kicking off the panel Joe. I
Got some you kick
Joe, I would kick you in the ball for peddily
Got it. That's what I was talking about. Yeah, I mean, I love fucking
I love when like clients are like the type that likes their balls clicked and shit. It's the best
Mine too
You like your boss you like your boss
I don't want to be rude, but it's I want to go join good times if I can see I feel so bad for me so old and like lonely
You're all the lonely
Joe you're gonna be too hot bitch you're gonna leave too hot bitches to join an old man. I
Wouldn't say too hot bitches. I'd say one and a half
Joe I am I'll be a bitch for you Joe
Wow
Just imagine Justin's sucking my feet
I love my feet sucked actually
Justin is a freak so
Girl, oh my god, I I need a stop. It's just I've had my feet sucked and oh I have not gone back since then
You probably got smaller feet than I do you look little
Girl, I'm five nine. I am too. Oh, I'm a ten and a half or an eleven
I wore men's shoes as a fucking that's two two sizes smaller and men's shoes
No dumbass
Please don't call me a dumbass. Thank you. Joe then bend over for me
Well, I've been there for spunky, but I'm not better for you Joe. You'll I'll make you bend over Joe
You want to bet you will I bet you won't Joe. Do you remember talking to me before or no?
Were you drunk tomorrow? I won't even remember who you are spunky, but it's nice. We have talked before
Funky Joe falls in love in the moment. It's like fifty-first days with Joe when you talk to him. It's like fifty-first days
Was I being nice at least when we talk
Me then too and I'm just saying it's not a good guy even I don't remember at least I talk nice to women
Christine fucking go suck a dick already Christine like fucking leave me the fuck alone bitch
No, would you ever talk about Christine like that? I'll fucking slap the shit out of you
Not my crap. Well you just slapped me but don't you put your little paws on Christine? I'll slap Christine too
All the minecraft really really want to like Christine like I do
Christine seems awesome
I already blocked her on YouTube the only reason why I'm seeing her comments is on this on stream
You're that's another reason why I'm seeing her comments
It's just I'm not even talking to the bitch and the bitch is still talking to me
Don't call her a bitch, by the way
Her photo is of a bitch you dumbass
Her photo is literally of a fucking bitch. It's a dog as her photo
She literally you're stupid I see your dog. It looks like Joker's dog
a bitch a bitch is a female dog therefore she is a bitch
If I want to be tentacle, it's a fucking bitch
Like seriously like
At this point she's fucking obsessed with me like she's obsessed with it. You're a tranny chaser Christine
You're a tranny chaser
But her actually sounds like you're the one that's obsessed flirty
So she's been talking to me this entire time in the comment section
She said a fucking word to ya
In the comment sections. Yeah, she has you dumbass. You're too fucking drunk to realize that
Yeah, I do jump to realize words
You are you're a fucking drunk just like Bita
Oh, don't you ever say that. Yeah. I went for the two for one right now. You want to call me gay you
would call me drunk. That's fine. Don't you ever compare me to beat up. That's what you're drunk.
Just like her. Let's talk about something. Call the police. Be a cop. Call her just like her.
I'm calling the cops. I'm going and you'll be a cop. Call her just like her then.
Hey, actually, put your man behind your back. You're going to jail.
Joe you don't have the balls to try. It's not funny anymore. You're actually going to jail. You don't have the balls Joe
Well, I got the keys to your jail cell
Joe, I'll put you in the fucking Chastity belt
If I was the prison officer like a prison warden
I would like see flirty so and I banged a little like the Billy Club one or like knock knock knock wake her up
Oh, whenever you knock whenever I know it's you knocking I would be jacking off just
You know what Joe just cuz Joe just cuz I know it'll be you knocking. I'll be jacking off just for you Joe. Don't worry
Yeah, I'll be jacking off just for you because I know it'll be you knocking on the fucking door
And actually Joe, I would be going to a female's prison actually so no
I'll meet you there
So you can't be awarded out of pre female prison Joe
So maybe it's a hateful honey, that's Joe. What's the fuck mean? He's jealous. I
Don't want to fuck you. I want to fuck it's like
Joe you guys got big. I see your eyes get wide-sighted. I see your eyes wide Joe
First of all, thank you doesn't take it up the ass like you
Oh, you weren't a bad. He doesn't hang on. He's
Thank you, do you take it up the ass exactly?
Like he's the top he has a shit in a slit of his dick from fucking his boyfriend, so he showed me this
What the fuck
The psyche only like a psyche only lets people see his butt, but nobody plays with his butt
He's just as people see it. Nobody ever touches psyche
Thank you. Oh my god, girl. If you were on if you're on discord
I was sending you fucking psyche in a speedo and a hospital thong money for 20. Why are you making that face?
Why is money for 20 making that throat face?
Like he literally went on after psyche found out that I did shower streams like he went in his veto and fucking started doing shower streams
I'm not on discord, but maybe I'll try
Yeah, psyche copies psyche started copying me about shower streams, and he went in a hole
He made his veto and excuse me. He made his veto into a fucking top. We're getting all choked up about the authority
Leave her alone, and then Sam and was really cute and then Sam man was watching him in the shower actually
He did I can send you a photo Joe
I guarantee, Sam, I do know what Sam said, man.
I guarantee it's a shadow watcher.
A shower.
Hanseki fucking Samman was watching you in the shower.
Yeah.
He was looking right there.
Alexander NYPD made Saeki make his fucking Saeki porn
bomb himself, actually.
But Alexander NYPD told Saeki to make his speed onto a thong
so Saeki did it.
And we all saw his hairy nuts.
What about that guy? How hairy were they?
Did you see the hairy nuts?
Yes, we all saw Psyche's hairy nuts.
We didn't see any nuts.
Yes, we did Psyche.
We literally saw your nuts when you made your speed onto a dog just for Alex.
I don't believe it.
Psyche, you ended your stream right after.
I didn't do it.
Yes, you did.
I'm sorry.
It's funny for me.
Like, was it really that funny?
Like retire your fake life.
Like it wasn't that fun.
Fine.
And again, you can't.
Joe, if you're fucking Mike, there's a fucking.
There's a what's it called?
There's an echo in your mind.
You have an echo.
There's an echo in your fucking balls.
Joe, I'll fucking show you my balls right now.
Do it.
Do it then.
Do it right now.
No, we'll go backstage and then I'll show you my balls
Is that Sam and you
Sam and you idiot
Joe you're fucking stupid, you know that
That's a fucked up part like I feel bad for him cuz he's a retard. So I tolerate
Yes
Can you hear me now? I cool. I got a question. I got a question for the toy older transmission up here real quick
Who's the Toyota Transmission?
Right here on the right up here to the right of me.
This Toyota Trans, Toyota Transant.
I don't drive Toyota.
What's your fucking question?
It's not your bitch's answer.
I ain't talking to you.
We don't like it.
It's not your bitch's answer.
I ain't talking to you.
You don't like Toyota.
It's not your bitch's answer.
I ain't talking to you before I chop your head off.
Shut the fuck up.
You're gay.
Eat my fucking ass.
Hey, listen.
A transmission listen, why you why you be trolling? Why you be being messy with your shit like that?
Why you do my girl like that Miguel whatever his name is why you do that messy shit?
Because I'm don't need people to be saying false shit
You don't feel like that's why you don't like this
I don't care I don't like you the person to be homeless in the crib and there's other checkup
Are you like Daffy duck with a big shot off?
Don't just like a piece of bologna
Cameron
My my shit looks good ain't no baloney over here
Ain't no baloney over here big dope. I
Got a nice hopping bra on like fucking
I wouldn't say they're nice, but psyche my booths are perfect and
Psychi knows that Joe knows that and so the spunky knows that I ain't got no fucking baloney
Everybody knows my boobs look good
There ain't no bologna on this chat
I just love that this retarded ASL tried to attack Sponkey when she's looking so good with her camera on and he's gonna come up and attack her
That's why nobody's going to turn their camera on
Re-throw, listen, never say what they say
This is why they don't turn their camera on
I do that
I'm gonna restart
That's why I love when Doug Dee comes at me and chat and I'm like, bitch, you ain't never been on camera
Don't be the bitch don't be the fucking homo if I don't mind saying no, it's a girl. It's a girl
So I don't care if it's a girl or not. I don't care what the fuck it is
Okay, I'm back. I'm back now. Like I had to
I had to sober up didn't work
You're looking more Latina as the night goes like she's getting like more Mexican
I showed my whole bra. That's why I had to restart myself
Because he
No, it was just my bra psyche
Just
Yeah, I had to I just had to fuck it had to sober
When I get too comfortable with my own body and like I'll show my whole bra
I'm not actually come to with it. I'm not come to with it yet. I'm not at Joe you Joe you love my body
I'm very uncomfortable right now
Joe you love you love that you saw my pink bra just now. I'm kidding. I'm very comfortable 30. I'm Joe
You love that you saw my hot pink bra. You're like damn
I wish I was in the middle row with both between you and spunky that'd be so hot between two sexy
So you're like damn she matches her she matches her pink bra with her pink panties her pink shirt her pink shorts
You're like
Fucking lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, they're from her head to her toes
We need Justin
Justin's gonna spoil up with you, Joe
You have a bad bitch
There was a point of relationship that I was like
If you can't handle a bad bitch just break up with me
Yeah
That happens they're together
Learning so what if you were rated demon do regime and do
You're trying to fucking I'm
I want to find out what are you doing? I need to got my charger. We know what you're doing, Psyche.
We know what you're doing. I want to hear the whole story. Alright, I'll be right back, guys. I'm going to get some bathroom.
Let me get my charger. Okay. Okay. Guys, we're gonna get some tea. I think slowly Diamond's gonna...
Who is that lady who is that lady on spunky's profile picture? That's it's obviously not her but
Oh, that's old me, okay?
Oh, is it really?
Show it again.
Let me see it.
Let me take a look at it.
Show it again.
I don't know, like three or four years ago.
Be nice.
Bye.
That's good, that's good.
Oh my God, that is nice.
You look really good.
Joe, do I look like my photo, Joe?
Do I at least look like my photo?
No, Ashley, you look hotter, Flirty Dimey.
You look even hotter in that photo.
Nigga, fuck you.
I'm just trying to give you a compliment asshole. No you said I look hotter in my fucking photo you fucking piece of shit
I said you look hotter. Christ. What do you want? It's not my photo. That's rude saying I look hotter in my photo
You know what? If I see that photo, I burn it. If I see that photo again, I'll burn it.
I'll fucking show you my fucking dick.
Oh, ooh, don't you threaten me with a good time.
You know what?
Saki, I saw all of Raging, and Raging has seen everything, but my princess wanded.
He turned around and showed me the back.
No
No, I've only seen raging's fucking dick and his like his stomach and like
Why does he have a man to bind his profile pictures that Amanda binds from Nickelodeon?
I never seen this fuck. I don't want to see his ass psyche. It's like a man
He didn't have his legs open a little bit
Have a spread
I've never seen his fucking butt
Okay
No, I never I just saw his fucking dick
Okay, all he saw all all reaching us in this my fucking tits in my ass. That's all he's ever saw
Geez nobody cares. I mean he saw my fucking asshole. I guess. Oh
Wow, you showed your asshole. Wow. What an animal my ass holes on fucking Twitter, Joe
I'm just saying you shouldn't show it. Like, what are you a fucking animal Josh? I'll send you the I'll send you the link to my
Hey, hey, Joe, no, I'm okay
Yeah, you're on a disc or she's gonna send you a disc or she's gonna send a photo the opener just for right away
They're they're Joe fucking are saying the link to their Joe look backstage and click on the link
I don't think I would have clicked that unless I got a fucking boner
You know you have a boner right now
With a boner just click it Joe I hear your reaction
Yes, I should leave my face
Click the link Joe click it. I'm not clicking to see your bottle weirdo
You know you'll lick my butthole
I don't even want to look at it. Let alone lick it. Calm down. Don't eat it
No, thank you. Yes, you would Joe
I'd rather eat Chinese food than your airy man-ass.
Joe, you literally said you're going to shove fucking 30 anal
beads out of your ass.
Well, we're talking about sponkeys-ass.
Give me a nap.
Joe, you literally said you're going to shove.
You were going to put.
Joe, you said you're going to put 30 anal beads up my ass
and then eat it out of my ass.
Yeah, well, the first part was true.
Joe, the whole audio was on my fucking channel.
It's all my fucking channel. You saying that you dumb fuck
Okay, I'm admitting I said it. I don't care. I was drunk and having fun like what's your oh, what's your sober your sober
actually
No, why would you why would you say that's why would you say that when you're sober?
You know why I said it because maybe I want to lick lick lick lick lick lick lick lick from her head to her ass, psyche
Do you do not want my toes suck?
Now you want to talk psych now you're away. No joke. I want my toes suck too. Thank you very much. Oh
Yeah
You're saying it's like we'll suck you I don't want thank you to suck my toes
Oh, you want me to? Oh, yeah, suck my toes Joe. Yeah. Yeah, why don't you want sight to do it because I'm way
I'm way hotter than sight. Thank you. Look at that. He doesn't have the skills. That's why I said he doesn't have the fucking skills
That's slavery right there. Where's the why?
Why do you have slavery added on you?
I
Have tattoos too. I have a frog right here. I have a fucking
I have butterflies right here and I have a fucking playboy bunny right here, and then I have a tramp
Then my tramp stamp says daddy's princess
Well, are we ready to have what's a reading right now? I want a reading about my sex life psyche
Okay, very good. I'm reading her sex life, please
Okay, well first I got for you
Have one the misty at the mystery. Okay, there's the treasure cat
With a little mystery I want him to I want him to fucking do that and expect it to me
All right
The mystery is like, you know, that's the high priestess and says the mystery represents wisdom and tuition and the subconscious
The card like the treasure cat carries the message that things are always what they seem the mystery advice
You got to take anything at face value dig deeper and use your intuition to discover what's really going on under the surface
Hey, time to consider a situation from new perspectives. You may discover the challenges you're perceiving
Aren't truly even there at all
Okay, and then we like it and none of us have to be fucking a nigga and like I gotta find out his real emotions after fucking him
Well, maybe that was well said psyche that the cards you just read that actually meant something to me
That was very well. I actually did like that. I'm just trying to translate it so I can understand
Yeah, and you have actually liked it then why don't you stop making all about yourself?
You have to tell the temperate the temperate there's a potion there. There's like a little
Okay, so I put a lusco on him
Maybe
Temperance is a lot about, you know, not going to extremes and to be, you know, also put
your energies together in a way.
that, you know, may be, um, unique, but I'm extreme though.
It's like, you're like, I'm extreme.
Thank you, camera.
You broke it.
I'm extreme.
I'm extreme though.
That's the thing.
I'm very extreme.
In Wonderland, Alice sometimes finds it difficult to reach the perfect balance between growing
bigger and smaller as she partakes in the transformational labeled body, bottle and cookies.
give and take and blending different elements together harmoniously. It suggests that you're
well on your way to creating the life you want. Now is no time for nonsense. Take care to stay
sensible as you manage all the tasks and projects you've been working on. It will eventually come
together and create success. It's important now to practice moderation and make sure you're
And moderation you got to eat ass. You can't always do it all the time or you know
I'm gonna I'm gonna read you about my sex life right now
There's no there's the aid of sword aid of swords is like you know
It's a kind of like can be that trapped in your own head card. It says eight of swords represents the feeling of being
Traps limited restricted to the keyword here is feeling they may feel as though you don't have an option or wait out of the situation
Spongy don't listen to them. You could talk adesaurus
do
Define them look at these from a different perspective
Okay, I mean I do get trapped in my head a lot cuz like
I'm an Aries and like what's in the cup
She's drinking that liquor
She's drinking that hard liquor
Yep
Okay, dr. Philly
Dr. Phil has a series called Phil in the Blanks, like PHIL.
Phil in the Blanks, it's about narcissists and narcissistic abuse, and you can check
out Encyclopaths and Machiavellians and all kinds of things, take on that series with
Dr. Phil.
So, how are we doing?
It's great.
Thank you.
It is great.
It's a good one.
You do think it'd be like you'd be like cheesy or not a good information because Dr. Phil, but it's actually like he had a really good
Yes, oh my gosh we're years
Russians
um so the moral of my fucking reading essentially i'm gonna have fun but the same time i need to get
for 10 years sweetheart hold on not to cut you off what happened to you sweetheart for 10 years
that's horrifying what happened to me i was married to a narcissist and i tried so hard to
make him happy and i never could well at least you're happy now that's all that matters yeah
Oh my God, meeting Justin, hands down.
I know you all want to pick on him or whatever.
The greatest thing that's ever happened to me.
Nice.
Remember when he was in NSYNC?
It's his name, Justin Chamberlain.
Remember when he said, bah, bah, bah, bah, bah, bah?
He did.
He said, bye, bye, bye, it's all in a hose.
And then said yes to me.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, sorry, girl.
Remember when you were in the band with Crisker Patrick?
That was pretty cool.
Yeah.
Do you remember?
Crisker Patrick?
Yeah.
And Jaycee Chavez, he was pretty hot.
There's like a mystery to your relationship.
I just need a ghetto translated psyche.
Okay.
Oh, you know what I mean, you know what I'm talking about.
I'm sorry, I'm set up.
No, not you, spunky. No, no, no.
We said there's mystery to be revealed in the relationship. There's
You know, maybe spending some time separated. It will be a key to it, but also
You know, you might feel trapped in your mind because you're not not meeting so maybe decided to always do what advice card for you
It's like some advice for you. This says okay, but at the emperor
So maybe he looks like he's a kind of a good guy. You're so sexy spunky. I'm actually
My gosh
It's gonna be a roller coaster pretty much and like it's just a matter of me getting out of my fucking head about shit
Yeah
TV show had a roller coaster in the theme song
Thank you. Don't interact with the children
I apologize
Yeah, I know you know what's funky. We're gonna have a fucking finger off. How many fingers you shove in your mouth
One finger up your mouth
I can fit my whole fingers in my mouth
Do it prove it prove it. Yeah, there you go prove it. Oh my god
You know what I so far I've been able to fit 10 fingers on my mouth spunky only five
Of my mouth. That's my mouth. You're talking about
My foods here
Like he did order food. I thought he didn't but look at psyche's butt. He just showed us a little butt just now
There's I swear to God it looked like yet a basement
Did you see
They said what's going on daddy
Daddy
Don't you call Oliver that don't you call Oliver Jabroni?
Daddy them kiddies. They want to know what's going on with that daddy jabroni. You're talking
I was calling you daddy shut up daddy Joe
Oh, I'll be your daddy, baby, but you just got to ask twice
Joe keep you my daddy
Yeah, you got to ask twice
Joe, I'll let you be my daddy
But that one the question that was more of a statement. That's like, oh, I know what I'm cuz I'm telling you
Zip your lips right now. I
Just want to look at spunky and like just look at her instead. Oh, no
I want to burn her face into my memory. I'm just trying to burn. You ever burn the memory
Okay, spunky people want to know do you know how to suck cock?
Let's ask the horses
He said now I'm good
But he had to teach me how to do it better
I
Never mind. I'm gonna say that never mind. Sorry fuck fuck. Yeah, I was going about to say how would he know how to
How's he gonna teach you?
One thing I love about psych is you wear shirts that look like my tablecloth on my kitchen table. Thank you
Thank you
Is that the shirt that you use? Do you use your tablecloth to clean up your knife?
Yeah, I use my Thanksgiving tablecloth
So he's wearing your fucking cum rag
You have your damn right he is
What do you got a problem with it?
Oh, I'm just trying to figure out what you're trying to imply
Set the fuck up boy. Yeah, you shut the fuck up. You shut the fuck up. You shut the fuck up fucking wigger
You're a wigger you're a wigger
Yeah, we got it right here. Oh my god. I love
I used to love going to Wendy's, Wendy's, let me say one thing, oh no, let me please
say one thing, back in 1992 or one or three, when you used to go to Wendy's, they had a
nice dining experience, they had nice chairs, nice tables, nice carpet, Wendy's used to
be the fucking dining experience for fast food.
What's the same thing we said before talking about, ain't nobody going there now and neither.
Joe, was this when you were writing Dynathors?
No, this is when Joe used to ride the dinosaurs 40, baby
I think Joe and I are the same age with all of his comments. How old? No, no, Joe is older than you
I've turned 40 year one years old. I'll be I'm 41 Joe. You're fucking older than 41. You just admitted to being 45
You were 45 like 40 minutes ago. You said you're 45
Like I remember what the fuck you say Joe you're fucking lying
Your guy thinks he's a woman and the last person I got a lie to is you I'm 41 years old you're the last
Joe and you look like a fucking you look like an old-ass fucking people you look like an old people
Oh
I am an expert in telling age bark for me bitch exactly let me see your balls
Exactly Joe. You're my good little bitch exactly
Who's a good little bitch who's my little bitch yes you are
These funky I told I told you he was my bitch told you I
Got fucking go under a sexy. I got under a love spell. I got you under a love spell Joe
Joe, what's up with the turning camera on and off? Just like I
Did turn it off because I thought you look like truthfully Trisha. That's who you look like so that's why it turns it off
Thank you. Um Joe. I I put bruja brought here on you. I did
I could speak fucking French
But you don't that Spanish you dumbass. Oh
Sorry about that
Yeah, I did bruja I did bruja shit on you Joe
Yeah, I fucking I grabbed the chicken I fucking went
You know where I live group and they were freaking out because they found dead chickens at the intersection
That was me with I guess like some odious thing. Yeah, it was you I knew it. Mm-hmm. I did it for just for Joe
Now let her talk it was 30. Well, you found dead chickens at the intersection. What happened with that?
Yeah, they were people were just freaking out
They were like
This is our topic but your nose is pierced
Yeah, that's why it's actually I just realized it like I was seeing some I get distracted by sparkly shit
So like my lip is
Come on YouTube a lot. It's very rare. You actually see a sexy woman like spunky like it's very
Actually, it's kind of rare. You actually see a good look Joe. You call every woman. You know sexy
I gotta say why can it's very nice to meet a sexy woman like spunky. I gotta say
I'm not trying to Joe you say this to every woman that you fucking know you
Tracy I feel like my fucking grandma
You know Tracy X no, she's my grandma on here. She has a she has a succubus tattoo over her pussy
No, she literally has an actual fucking she has a champ stamp over her. I have
Joe mama over my pussy
I
Mean that's better than my tramp stamp my tramp stamp says daddy's princess. So that's cute. That's cute
But no, I'll be like it's in cursive at the bar at the bar. I'll be like, hey, I'll see like I rolled up on Justin
I was like Justin
You know, it's funky at the bar. I'd be like, baby. I want to take you home. She's like, why?
I like I want to let your pussy for 19 hours. That's what I want to know. You're ruined it wouldn't work on you
Joe shut up. You ruined it. You're like stop ruining shit Joe. I set it up. I set it up and you gosh
But I was like, hey
You know Joe and they'd be like Joe who and I'd be like
Don't you know Joe mama
But you fucking flirty fuck up. She's about to show her ass cheeks
Spunky I thought you're actually
I wouldn't judge you I actually would be laughing
My god, I was ready, but I wasn't ready
I knew it. I knew you were ready for it.
I knew you were ready for it.
Amber, it's gonna win.
I was ready to a degree about this.
I was ready to a degree.
Who's up here between the sexy ladies, Oliver?
Who's between the two sexy women on panel?
I am, Oliver.
You're in the chat talking to Amber.
Joe is.
Joe, I rather have, I rather have Psyche in the middle.
I rather have Psyche in the middle.
I'll tell you right now, I'd fucking eat spunky farts right now.
Y'all, don't you make a weird face, Clarity.
Don't be jealous.
Hear what I said.
You heard exactly what I said.
What the fuck?
You.
It's wrong with you.
Where is that gay guy Oliver
Jabroni is he in chat because I'm pretty sure he's gay.
Hang on I just want to confirm.
Okay I'm back I just had to like.
I'm excited because Joe said he'd eat my farts.
No, I had to process that.
Yeah, Joe, hang on, hang on.
You'd eat my farts?
Joe!
For them in a mason jar, and I'll open the jar and be like, oh, what's that smell?
You're so easy. I tell Justin about men like you in the world
So what is
I don't need to be come back. I know you're gonna rethink the fart comment
Did you shot yourself?
What did he? Yeah, she tried to or she shit herself. Wow
So one time
I farted in the middle of the night like on accident, you know, like in your sleep
It's just like fucking it's cute. It just happens like whatever, right? Oh
Very the mirror very the mirror like whatever, you know, it just fucking happens Justin and I are snuggling
It's like we're sleeping. It's like fine
Go ahead. I'm listening. All right. I wake up and I'm like
Shit
Oh shit, it's self-justice
I farted and then fucking just woke up and Justin. How was that part?
It was so bad I woke him out of a dream and he woke up and he was like what the
He was fucking wrecked him
No, no, let me say one thing, Justin didn't even listen to you, Justin didn't even answer
you when you asked him, if you were to let me talk, let me talk, yeah, so if you would
afford it on me, I would have waited till we got married and I would have took the microphone
like listen, I knew I was in love with this lady the first time she shittled me and farted
right in my fucking nose, and you're like, you're right, Joe, you're right, she's a good
Joe, I see I always think you surprised me Joe, but then like you fucking pull out another wild card
That's too surprising
Yeah, like I'm used to what you say, but then you pull out a wild card
This is a wild card for me this is part of the course. Oh
My god
Anybody hear that no
Fractured trailer grinding its gears. No, I am getting tired of you fucking turning your camera on and then turning that off and then turning
I'm sorry, it's funky, but you farted on cam. I was fucking reclip it. I'm sorry
I can smell it I just don't stop you're causing me to have seizures stop fucking turning your camera off and on
Joe my camera, but that's what I look like. No, you're a face looks like just join us
Oh, we're gonna kick you off the island
And why are you holding your phone like just place it down like a normal person
Nigga shut the fuck up if you want me on camera, I don't need you to tell me how to hold my fucking phone to be honest listen here cracker
Listen here, sir
You're a cracker
You you miss her you think you're you think my tractor sexy fucking looking at
You know Joe fucking sit on it and bounce
I just want every gay guy in the chat to know who's up here in between both of the sexiest ladies
Look at who is up here me and all the gay guys in the chat are like, oh Joe's gay
Who's in the middle of the tits boys?
Thank you
Justin there you go Joe. I'm teasing you there you go
I'm too drunk right now. I'm literally too drunk right now. Like I'm already halfway done with my second beatbox and like
It's hitting me harder and harder
J.T. Joe, I have a tool. I'm gonna fucking circumcise you
circumcise you yeah
Joe stop I told you about your fucking camera already Joe
I'm turning off. No, both of us told you by your camera. You see this thing?
It's never been in a butthole, but it's gonna be in yours. Oh, I got I got three things.
Whoever just said who's that gay dude in the middle? It's obviously like crack it down or somebody on an
alt. They're not even man enough to say who they are. They're like
You know that's funky
Just like my dick before actually I never fuck it. Oh, so you have a dick say you're a minute you have a cock
Okay, weird. I never sucked it, but you're weird. Yeah, you did Joe
You want a bet I whipped it out backstage and you opened your mouth
Did you oh, I thought that was like a little twig. I thought that's like a twig you found in the ground
Everybody saw my dick just now every cell the outline just now. I got a big ass thick thick every solid just now
You want to see it again Joe you want to see it again you want to see it again Joe
I'll show you my dick again Joe
You know what? I'll stand up again, Joe. Just for you. I'll show you my hard fucking dick right now. There you go, Joe. Just for you.
Thank you, baby. Oh, wow. That's obviously not a Coke bottle. That's her dick. That's her dick, by the way.
It is my dick. Duh. Just for you, Joe.
Just for you.
Joe that was just for you, so don't be mad
God, I appreciate that. Thank you for showing me your dick. That's really gentlemen of you and drink your beer out of a
Girl the orange one got me more fucked up
Like
Went to one when I was on 18 actually they're like bailing I did like a bunch of glitter highlight on my on my face
And like right here and like my neck
Fuck I'm old, but I don't I wore I wore a crystal clear skirt
Yeah, my this guy wore it was like sparkly but clear, you know, yeah
Just in his first EDC
This year and he had the fucking time of his life. I went there on LSD. It was very fun
No, I know your doctor so like you can't do LSD and shit, but like yeah, if you ever if you ever get the chance
I
Never done LSD. Um, I've done I've done shrooms that
I can't do I can't do actual shrooms like I can micro dose shrooms, but if I actually do a real dose of shrooms I get paranoid. Oh
They made me paranoid, but like not not my thing not my thing I
Already said why I dropped the DMs already
somebody sent me a fucking video of fucking rage and calling me a Fred and I thought it was actually him saying it and
Y'all got the best of me. Oh, well, y'all got the best of me for one fucking minute
Y'all got the best of me and then I realized it wasn't him saying it
Even though you're a guy we still love you. It's alright Joe suck my dick from the back
Why are you saying that it's kind of weird? I'm not gonna suck
I don't give a fuck Joe. You suck my dick for
Joe you suck my dick multiple times
Wow, you know what I'm calling the police wait so one time we should give Joe a kiss. You ready? Okay?
Don't put your big-ass head in the middle
No, you gotta turn around spunky
The other way you're both wrong turn the other way dumbass
There you go
Proof
Someone just said we're the balls and Joe is the pee-pee in the middle hang on. Let's be the balls
I'm gonna hear balls. I can't make balls
Girl, I I know need to know how to make a dick with my number that was my real dick never mind
Take a look at this fuck you
There it is, there it is, there it is, right there.
Take a look at that.
I don't like, I hate that.
Hang on, hang on, hang on, Justin.
Take your nail.
It's over.
Why?
I'm in love with Joe.
Hey, Justin, your girlfriend gave me a little kiss on my cheek.
It felt so good.
It felt really good.
It's over.
I just saw Joe's dick and it was so...
Did we just witness a breakup in real life?
He said I believed it if he said you were going to go with flirty.
I guess I turned you into girls, but...
I'm all over it girl. I'm a I'm a spunky like chicks with dicks now. I convert everybody
I mean I'll look I'll experiment for the one time
You know, I'll entertain it just to say I did but as long as we can record it for only fans
Like to take you for a cookout sweetheart or fireworks
I like to get the fireworks by a nice dinner
Give you little kiss on your cheek to pay you back for my case you gave me
Another was another where she was trying we're competing with
Spunky in other words Joe was trying to watch his fuck for free pretty much in other words
That's the translation. He's just trying to watch for free
That's the English translation. That's the translation, but what do you think about?
Oh my god, I hope this doesn't get re-clipped
No, I don't want this reclip, this is like the worst
I'm too drunk for this
I
Am too drunk for this Joe. All right. I'm fucking around
Beer I've been up here for five hours. I ain't seen a drink one drop of alcohol, but you're drunk. That's kind of weird
Great now I got all my fucking screen nice bow tie in your hand boy
No, it's a butter. It's bunch of butterflies and then it's there's the both right and I have a bow tie right here
She's always right here, Joe
Grow up grow up for you
On your like right here. Um, yeah, I'll show you my tattoos. Um,
Right here, it's a frog
With a cowboy hat
And then
Here
Don't be an asshole those are cute it's a play with money and some butterflies. Yeah
Don't be a dick I have weird
I have a kiss mark on my ass, honestly.
No, actually, well, I'm sitting on wood, literally.
No, I literally have lip prints on my ass.
They're just in.
Oh!
I'm kidding, I won't show you my tramp stamp,
because I will pull my shorts too down,
and I'm not trying to have this stream get ended.
Yeah, but I have a bunch of fucking random ass tattoos like I have a goat. Look at that. That's a fucking random
Love the heart. Yeah, it's a twin flame tattoo. It's my tattoo for Justin
Like I'm actually gonna get a heart on this side. This is my slutty side and this is my fun side
Dia de los Muertos. Oh, I love that. Isn't it beautiful with a lotus? Yes
Yeah, I fucking love it. It's hard to see it on here like the details. No, we can see it fully psyche. Um, he full-screen deal
Oh, it's it's fun. It's fun. It's a good tattoo. It's pretty. Yeah, um, I'm actually gonna get the birth of paradise over here
That's so cool, you have nice tattoos, but
Yeah, I'm kind of sad because my better tattoos are lower, but I won't share them
Because I want to fucking
I'm going to get your name tattooed on my dick spunky. That's how big my dick is. It's spunky. And that's why we'll be right on tip.
Joe, would you get a diamond tattoo for me, Joe?
No, that's too far. I'm not going.
Why? It's my birthstone.
I'll get what you need, but I'm not going to do it for free.
I'll get a pimple for you.
Because I call you a pit bull remember
Yeah, I'll get a pit bull tattoo just for you
All right, fair enough. Oh, well you get a diamond tattoo if I get a pit bull tattoo
Oh, I was saying you a picture of my dick and you tell me right where you wanted right babe. What?
What do you mean why don't you get the tattoo you just tell me right where you want it just gotta be be honest
I don't want to get it on my balls or because I got big I don't say I got big balls, but
like they're fucking so big they're annoying Joe, Joe, Joe, I got a situation like why
don't my balls again why they got to be so big right if you and I are going for a walk
Are the imprints left behind our footprints and your balls or just our footprints?
You like pina coladas and making love?
I would get down on my knee if I was walking with Spunky on a beach and I would say Spunky, fuck Justin, will you marry me, baby?
That's what I would say.
Oh my god, Justin, you heard that?
Well, I think I married Justin.
Alright.
Daddy said I gotta go. Bye guys, have a good night.
That was the ultimate thing.
Bye!
Bye, have a good night, Flirty. I'll see you later, honey.
See you later? Are you leaving me on here with him?
I know I'm sorry, but...
He's boss, but I'm sorry. I'm sorry
You're not letting Joe and I have a freak off now Psyche
Can't be here with this guy. I just can't deal with this guy. Nice to meet you though. Goodbye. Oh
Where's everyone going? Oh, okay. We're here Joe left
What an ass wipe
Yeah
He's gonna leave Joe
Joe got shot. She's a he's shy of the freak off again
I made Joe do too many things backstage and now he's scared of what I'll make him do again
I know he never really never really invited. I always I always they say kick from studio when uh, and uh, he goes backstage
You always
We're actually never was we're ready for the free coffee to take from the studio. So it's just like, you know, I
Had a freak off once a Joe
Yeah
It was everything
It was it was wrinkly. It was wrinkly. It was a red
It was pink. It was pink. Okay
Yeah, one it's just it was nasty
Did it look like a blind mole mole rat?
I look like a piece of salmon. Oh my gosh, Joe. Yeah, now Joe left. He invited someone to go up
stage and then he left. Like what the fuck? I don't see him backstage. I don't see him backstage.
Oh my god, he's backstage with uh with with Raging Demon. Raging Demon is not actually up here.
He's I know he's backstage. He's with you and Joe. Yeah, that's not the real Raging Demon. He's
Yeah, well Joe's Joe's walking around his bed and touching him. Oh my god, Reggie. Do you have a no no?
I understand thank you. I thought the real Regine. Okay. Okay. Yeah, yeah, okay gulanders smiling. Hey guys. Oh
my god, don't have a membership tonight and then uh
Yeah, we're gonna have a lot more members who's gonna buy sake fish tacos tonight. Even though he did just get I
Don't think I don't think anybody but it's okay. I
I'm full on Wendy's. Hey, what's up Nick? Are you how ours has Nate?
I always get the biggie bags the biggy
Hey
What's up, you know good, you know Chris you're floating diamonds. I actually don't know Chris
He's promoting his rumble. I never met you summer. I
Never met you Chris
Or a listen where you been bro everything the fucking come on man
He knows you psyche, but he doesn't know me I guess I mean, we'll meet them. Yeah
No, I don't I actually I'm being for real. I never met Chris. Well, say hi introduce yourself. Hey girl
Uh-oh. Chris is a guy.
I don't know. I'm just...
I'm drunk.
What are you drinking? What are you drinking on?
This is my orange beatbox.
Well, I was trying to show him but...
This is my orange beatbox, and this is my
Red beatbox my fruit punch one, and I keep spilling something's you know
There's a hole in the fucking fruit punch one because it keeps spilling
I saw a guy. What's up, Chris?
Everyone's three men and a woman on the panel holler
You see that you see the statement with the spunky and uh Joe that was classic. Uh,
No, I'm in seven today today
I missed it. Well
Yeah, go ahead
Wait, uh, filthy you're are you uh, are you trans?
Florida flirty flirty
Yeah, I don't lie about being trans my whole page. That's hashtag trans
I'm just curious because I mean, uh, I was wondering I'm not I'm not I'm not a homophobe. Like I said, uh, Sykes my homie, bro
Yeah, I'm I'm honest about being trans on my entire platform. I talk about my dick on my entire platform. So
Okay
Yeah, I'm just curious, you know
But hey, where's where's Paige, bro?
Hey, I don't know what pages that work right now. I think page is working
Maybe like, you know cleaning up the work right now. She was on earlier last I was talking to her last time
I don't mean to interrupt you guys. We're okay. Let me save a I was talking last time fucking and my internet ripped and
Fucked in I didn't mean to like leave
But yeah, I want to like I want to like, yeah, I don't want to
Have you met summer Chris or no
I don't know, but let me, let me finish what I was saying, like, uh, I wanted to, like, uh, because I was trying to get, like, uh,
if she, I was like, you were coming to Vegas, like, hit me up, and I wanted to, like, hang out, like, uh,
I would take her to, like, some, like, you know, concerts and shit like that.
Okay, hold on, hold on.
Hey, Flirty, what do you think? You want to go to a concert with him? He wants to take you out, he said.
No.
In Vegas.
Why not?
Because I'm all concert out.
You're all concerted out. What if he takes you to the strip and like you go gambling and then I already been to the strip
Well, I'm not talking about why don't I call her filled? Why is this a filthy?
It's a splurty. Is this flirty, but let me ask you Chris. Have you been with the trans people?
No
No, but are you here with your words to try?
Try I mean I like pussy, but uh
It's crazy. Let me be honest. It's crazy because I've seen like some, you know
I'm just like is that a girl like I'm like wow like I was like whoa
Okay, so there's a curiosity there oh
My god, you're I'm straight, but you're my first chance that I've ever been attracted to oh my god
well
I think he's being nice
Yeah
Fat look like titties bitch
Remember that.
It's a real motherfucker woman, bitch.
Real woman, bitch.
Real woman. You gotta buy a dick, bitch.
Remember that.
So what do you think about look for Chris? What do you think?
Remember that
What is this what's this is that you
Blabby long ass wait, there's a better one
What about that nasty-ass belly right there, bitch?
Okay, well, that's like-
Yeah, bitch.
Shut the fuck up. I don't give a fuck. I'm still kissing a bitch and still look better than you bitch. Holler
Hey guys, I ain't pussy better than any motherfucker on this panel. No that
Holler, that is an updated photo bitch. That was not that long ago. Holler. Actually, that's very old actually
You still look raft it you're still looking at two months ago, bitch big-ass big-ass big-ass stomach two months ago
Okay, suck my fucking dick
Well, I'm good, bitch. I'm straight. Go stick it in some of my eyes.
Suck my dick, bitch.
You wish. Never, bitch.
Suck my motherfucking dick, you fucking raggedy ass.
Never. Never. Never.
Never, bitch. Suck my dick.
Just remember, I'm the bitch you're trying to be, bitch.
Remember that I'm not trying to be you bitch. Remember that you want to be a woman bitch. I'm not jealous over you some more. I will never be jealous over you. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. I'm not jealous of you. You are a sorebop bitch. I'm not jealous of you. You are a sorebop bitch. I'm not jealous of you. You are a sorebop bitch. I'm not jealous of you. I'm not jealous of you. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop bitch. You are a sorebop
I'm not jealous of you somewhere, like you're literally old.
Letters your show my whole ball stocking your
Flabby ass stomach no you literally you can see my boss in that photo actually you literally form bomb psyche
Guys guys come back to the stream i'm gonna delete this one right to the stream like he literally should form bomb do something